<resources>
  <string name="app_name">QUANTUM PHOTONICS CLUB</string>
  <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
  <string name="navigation_view_header_text">team@quantumphotonics.club</string>
  <string name="text_fragment_title">Home</string>
  <string name="list_fragment_title">Event</string>
  <string name="pager_fragment_title">About Us</string>
  <string name="toolbar_icon_description">Icon</string>
  <string name="placeholder_text">
        QUANTUM PHOTONICS\n
        Empower Human Intelligence Worldwide\n
        through STEM\n
        We believe all human beings can embrace who they are, can\n
        define their future, and can change the world, regardless of\n
        backgrounds, race, ethnicity, gender, religion, social standing,\n
        income levels etc.\n\n
        Founder Message\n
        Welcome to Quantum Photonics Club! \n\n
        Being consistently touched and inspired by true, unconditional,\n
        universal love, I know deeply how love dramatically changes my\n
        entire life. I am very privileged to be raised up with the \n
        incredible love of my grandparents, a man who devotes his \n
        life to watching me grow up and a woman who shows a big \n
        heart and pure kindness to everyone unconditionally.\n
        Their love literally saves my soul and makes me have\n
        the strength to conquer all unknown challenges. I am fortunate\n
        enough to have got the best education opportunities and found my\n
        true love and passion of physics. I am especially deeply\n
        obsessed with exploring the truth of nature and life\n
        using my physics knowledge. With the inspiration of\n
        my grandfather, who always teaches me to think out of\n
        boxes, and think beyond the limits of conventional wisdom, and with\n
        the love of quantum photonics field, I finally got the courage to build\n
        this beloved Quantum Photonics Club, to pass on his spirit and love,\n
        starting from April 24th, 2021.\n\n
        I have to say this is one of the best things in my entire life. Its a\n
        wonderful experience for me to bring so many brilliant brains to learn\n
        and share with each other. We have covered multidisciplinary topics -\n
        quantum physics, neuron photonics, brain-computer interfaces,\n
        longevity, machine learning, quantum consciousness and beyond. I am\n
        so inspired by our every room discussions and happy to see we are\n
        making a difference by sharing our innovative and fascinating ideas\n
        openly and freely.\n\n
        Its totally OK if you are not an expert in this field, or you are totally new\n
        to our topics. You are right at home! No worries - Its our mission to\n
        I thought what I\d do was I\d pretend I was one of those deaf-mutes.\n
        help you think big and creative, reach your potential and fulfill your\n
        dreams. All we ask for everyone is to join us with the deep love of\n
        nature, life and especially the love itself.\n\n
        Last but not the least, special thanks for everyone who loves our club\n
        and shows trust and support when we were at the very beginning. I am\n
        honored to build with our beloved club continually with all of you. I\n
        hope Quantum Photonics Club could be a safe place for those we love\n
        and the ones they love, and I cant wait to have this amazing journey\n
        with all of you together. \n\n
        Please feel free to recommend us to anyone awesome and I am sure\n
        they will end up thanking you very soon enough. Cheers.\n\n
        With Love,\n
        Sierra\n
        June 2rd, 2021 \n
    </string>
  <string name="placeholder_text1">
        Space Medicine and Astronautics \n
        w Dr Shawna Pandya \n\n
        Space medicine is the practice of medicine on astronauts in\n
        outer space whereas astronautical hygiene is the application\n
        of science and technology to the prevention or control of\n
        exposure to the hazards that may cause astronaut ill health.\n
    </string>
  <string name="title_activity_register">RegisterActivity</string>
  <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
  <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
  <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
  <string name="next">Next</string>
  <string name="previous">Previous</string>

  <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
  <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
</resources>
